<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
and open the template in the editor.
-->


<messages>
    <template>
        <tempID>45559</tempID>
        <shortForm>SSLC Wishes</shortForm>
        <description>
            Dear Parent, we wish your ward All The Best for the SSLC Exam. From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.
        </description>
    </template>
     <template>
        <tempID>45558</tempID>
        <shortForm>RTE Notification</shortForm>
        <description>
            RTE Parents, bring all original documents of your child for RTE application verification on (Date) @ (Time) . From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.
        </description>
    </template>
	<template>
        <tempID>45406</tempID>
        <shortForm>Function Notification</shortForm>
        <description>
           Dear Parent, (Function / Competition) will be held on (Date) at (Time) in School Premises.Kindly send your child to school on time to be a part of the (Function/Competition). Thank You. From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.
        </description>
    </template>
	<template>
        <tempID>45404</tempID>
        <shortForm>Vacation Notification</shortForm>
        <description>
        Dear Parent, (Summer/Winter) vacation starts from (Start_date) and reopens on (End_Date). Thank You. From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.  
        </description>
    </template>
	<template>
        <tempID>45403</tempID>
        <shortForm>Holiday Notification</shortForm>
        <description>
          Dear Parents, (Date) will be holiday on occasion of (Reason for holiday). Thank You. From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.
        </description>
	</template>
		<template>
        <tempID>45402</tempID>
        <shortForm>PT Notification</shortForm>
        <description>
          Dear Parents, Parents Meeting is going to be held on (Date) at (Time). Please attend without fail. Thank you. From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.
        </description>
	</template>
		<template>
        <tempID>45401</tempID>
        <shortForm>Result Notification</shortForm>
        <description>
          Dear Parents, the results of (Mid Term/Annual Exams) will be announced on (Date) at (Time). Thank you. From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.
        </description>
	</template>
		<template>
        <tempID>45400</tempID>
        <shortForm>Exam Notification</shortForm>
        <description>
          Dear Parents, The (Mid Term/Annual Term) Exams will begin from (Start date) to (End date). Thank you. From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.
        </description>
	</template>
		<template>
        <tempID>45399</tempID>
        <shortForm>Unit Test Notification</shortForm>
        <description>
          Dear Parents, The (Unit test number) will begin from (Start date) to (Exam Date). Thank you. From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.
        </description>
	</template>
		<template>
        <tempID>45397</tempID>
        <shortForm>Fee Payment Notification</shortForm>
        <description>
          Dear Parents, you are requested to pay the (First Term/Second Term)  fee before (Date). Ignore if already paid. Thank you. From: Rajeshwari Higher Primary English Medium School, Yadgiri.
        </description>
	</template>
		
</messages>
